Guide to the Office of Institutional Advancement Records RG 7
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series I. Office of Alumni Affairs
  - Photographs
    - Events
      - Reunion: Class of 1954, posed (unlabeled), 1994 (Box 1.8, Folder 11)
      - Reunion: Class of 1960, posed (unlabeled), 2000 (Box 1.8, Folder 12Two 5x7 color w/negatives)
        Two 5x7 color w/negatives
      - Reunion: WXCI Radio Reunion, scanned images (labeled), 2000 (Box 1.8, Folder 13)
        Five 4 x6 color w/negatives
      - Reunion: Alpha Delta Pi Ten Year Reunion, (unlabeled), 2000 (Box 1.8, Folder 14)
        Three 4x6 color
      - Thomas, Al, Memorial: Groups, candids and posed (unlabeled), 1998 (Box 1.8, Folder 15)
      - Visitors: Jane Goodall, candids (includes Pres. J. Roach, Denise Hogan), 1998 (Box 1.8, Folder 16)
      - Visitors: Anita Shreve, author, ca.2000 (Box 1.8, Folder 17)
      - Unknown: Groups, candids and posed (unlabeled), ca.2000 (Box 1.8, Folder 18)
        Two 4x6 color
    - Events - 2011 Accession, RG6.xx___x
      - Ancell School, Marketing Certificates, Dave Heneberry, Feb 20, 2003; RG6.xx_2_1_x (Box 2, Folder 1)
        Two CDs and nine 4x6 color
      - Cashier's Deparatment, Joan ? Retirement, undated; RG6.xx_2_2_x (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Centennial Annual Report, 2002; RG6.xx_2_3_x (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Centennial Time Capsule, 2003; RG6.xx_2_4_x (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Commencement, President's Breakfast, 2001; RG6.xx_2_5_x (Box 2, Folder 5)
        25 4x6 color
      - Commencement, Faculty Breakfast/Employee of the Year (Sarah Baywood), 2001; RG6.xx_2_6_x (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Commencent, Dallas Beal with medal recipients, speakers, students, and guests, May 1, 2003; RG6.xx_2_7_x (Box 2, Folder 7)
        69 4x6 color
      - Commencement, Students, faculty, speakers, medal recipients, guests, May 1, 2003; RG6.xx_2_8-14_x (Box 2, Folder 8-14)
        248 4x6 color
      - Communique, October 2002: Centennial Kick-Off Celebration (Pres. James Roach with award recipient, Danbury Mayor Mark Boughton; Recreation of Legendary Ruth Haas Tea; Ruth Haas Tea; Storytelling for all ages/Prof. William Joel; CTA production of Shalamazoo; Photographic display in Alumni Hall; Jurg Lanzrein workshop on 9/14/02)), RG6.xx_2_15_x (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Communique, December 2002: Centennial Homecoming and Governor Rowland/State Bond Commission, Oct 1, 2002; RG6.xx_2_16_x (Box 2, Folder 16)
        Nine 4x6 color
      - Communique, February 2003: Macricostas Family Pledge, Jan 15, 2003; RG6.xx_2_17-20_x (Box 2, Folder 17-20)
        59 4x6 color
      - Communique, February 2003: Holocaust Forum; Jazz Ensemble, Nov 1, 2002; RG6.xx_2_21_x (Box 2, Folder 21)
        12 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Communique, March 2003 Issue, unlabeled, Mar 3, 2003; RG6.xx_2_22_x (Box 2, Folder 22)
        Three 4x6 & one 4x4 color; one 4x6 b/w
      - Communique, April 2003, Centennial 5K Committee, Feb 4, 2003; RG6.xx_2_23_x (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Communique, April 2003: Centennial Celebration, Mar 3, 2003; RG6.xx_2_24-25_x (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
        81 4x6 color
      - Communique, April 2003: Gerentology Task Force, Feb 20, 2003; RG6.xx_2_26_x (Box 2, Folder 26)
        10 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Dr. James Roach, Honorary Degree, Doctors of Laws, from Briarwood College, May 1, 2003; RG6.xx_2_27_x (Box 2, Folder 27)
        Ten 5x7 color
      - Unknown events, unlabeled, ca.2002; RG6.xx_2_28_x (Box 2, Folder 28)
        22 4x6 and one 5x7 color
      - Unknown Dr. Roach in Delphi Greece, 2003; RG6.xx_2_29_x (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - CPD Display 5/24/06, 2006; RG6.xx_2_30_x (Box 2, Folder 30)
        One CD and photocopies of pictures
    - Administration - 2012 Accession
      - Dr. James Roach Inauguration w/ Dr. Denise Hogan, Mr. and Mrs. Dallas Beale, posed, Oct 1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        Inauguration w/Dr. Denise Hogan, Mr. and Mrs. Dallas Beale, posed
      - Dr. James Roach Vintage portraits, posed, ca 1995 (Box 2, Folder 32)
        Two 4x5, six 5x7 b/w; 3 4x6 color
      - Dr. James Roach Event unknown (possibly in Belgium), ca 1998 (Box 2, Folder 34)
        One 4x6 color Two 4x5, six 5x7 b/w; 3 4x6 color
        - Dr. James Roach portraits, posed, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
          28 4x6 color (Photographer Mike Duffy)
      - James Roach, portraits, posed, Aug 2002 (Box 2, Folder 35)
        32 5x5 color w/negatives
    - Events - 2012 Accession
      - Alumni News Generation Photographs, Fall 2003 (Box 2, Folder 36)
        Four 4x6 color
      - Centennial ? Outdoor Group (unlabeled), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 37)
        Three 4x11 panoramic, color
      - The College of The Bahamas First Graduation Exercises, Dec 3, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Faculty Picnic, posed and candids (labeled and unlabeled), Aug 28, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
        26 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Alumni Picnic, individuals and groups (unlabeled), Jun 7, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 40)
        22 4x6 color
      - Fuel Cell Bill, Dr. Roach, Chancellors Carter and Cibes, Aug 25,1995 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - 4th of July at Ives Concert Park, Drs. Roach and Hogan with Ruth Henderson, ca 1996 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Funding for Science Building, Dr. Roach, Governor Rowland, Mayor Boughton and others, Oct 23, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 43)
        12 3.5x5 color (State of Connecticut photographs)
      - Funding for Science Building, Dr. Roach, Governor Rowland, Mayor Boughton and others, Oct 23, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 44)
        55 4x6 color
      - Goodall Institute, Dr. Roach and Jane Goodall signing agreement, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 45)
        Eleven 4x6 color
      - Goodall Board of Directors Meeting, Dr. Roach, Jane Goodall and board members, June 1996 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Hale Bopp Comet, ca 2000 (Box 2, Folder 47)
        One 4x6 and one 7x7 color
      - Homecoming, Dr. Roach and Gene Eriquez, posed, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Homecoming, outdoor events, posed (unlabeled), 2003 (Box 2, Folder 49)
        Seven 4x6 color
      - International Association of University Presidents Meeting, Dr. Roach with participants (unlabeled), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 50)
        Sixteen 5x7 color
      - Ives Halloween Masquerade, Drs. Roach and Hogan, Skitch Henderson, Richard Gerber, Mayor Eriquez, ca 1996 (Box 2, Folder 51)
        Six 4x6 color
      - Peoples' University, Beijing, Drs. Roach and Hogan w/participants, posed, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - President's Reception, ca 1997 (Box 2, Folder 53)
        20 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Recognition Dinner, Dr. Roach, faculty and staff, posed and candids, June 6, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 54)
        74 4x6 color
      - Reunion, Class of 1940 (labeled), June 8, 1990 (Box 11)
        97 4x5 color in 3-ring binder (Photographs by Thyra I. Salonen)
      - Reunion, Class of 1951 (unlabeled), fall 2001 (Box 2, Folder 55)
        27 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Reunion: Class of 1951 (unlabeled), 2001 (Box 2, Folder 56)
        24 4x6 color (Donated by Ann McKeon Lombardo)
      - Reunion, Class of 1953 (unlabeled), 2009 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - Reunion, Class of 1961 (unlabeled), Sept 15, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Reunion, Class of 1963 (unlabeled), Sept 2003 (Box 2, Folder 59)
        21 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Reunion, Class of 1969 (unlabeled), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - Commencement, outdoor, processional, speakers, students and faculty, posed and candids (unlabeled), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 61)
        24 5x7 color (Photographs by Chappell Studio)
      - Retirement Party, faculty and staff, posed and candids, Sept 26, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 62)
        60 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Visitor, Jesse Jackson, Jr., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - Visitor, George J. Mitchell, President's Lecture Series, April 2003 (Box 2, Folder 64)
        One 4x6 and one 5x7 color
      - Unknown event: Dr. Roach, Governor John Rowland, F.Muska, and others (Photo signed by Governor John G. Rowland), Aug 25, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - Unknown event: University Presidents w/ Chancellors Cibes and Carter, posed, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 66)
        One 8x10 color (Photographer Bob Hennessy)
      - Unknown event: Dr. Roach with Governor Rowland and unknown woman, posed, ca 1996 (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - Unknown event: Dr. Roach w/ Jodi Rell, posed, ca 1997 (Box 2, Folder 68)
        One 8x10 b/w
      - Unknown event: Drs. Roach and Hogan with Skitch and Ruth Henderson, posed, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 69)
        One 8x10 color (Photographer Steve J. Sherman)
      - Unknown event: Dr. Roach, Dr. Denise Hogan, and Walter Cronkite, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      - Miscellaneous (unlabeled), ca 2000 (Box 2, Folder 71)
      - Presdent Bill Clinton's visit, Sep 11, 2000 (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_808616a6b8a1b7858160c511b781d7fa)
    - Student life
      - General
        - Students Around Campus: Outdoor, posed, labeled/unlabeled (Mary Jane Hopkins, Frank Perry, William Nyerick), 1947 (Box 1.8, Folder 19)
          Nine 2.5 x 3.5 b/w
        - Athletics: Men's Basketball, Madison Square Garden (unlabeled), ca.2000 (Box 1.8, Folder 20)
        - Music Performing Group: Group unknown (unlabeled), 1995 (Box 1.8, Folder 27)
          16 4x6 b/w w/negatives
        - Homecoming: Sigma Chi, group posed (unlabeled), 1997 (Box 1.8, Folder 21)
        - Homecoming: Candids and group posed, women (unlabeled), 1997 (Box 1.8, Folder 22)
        - Homecoming: Candids (unlabeled), 1998 (Box 1.8, Folder 23)
        - Homecoming: Candids and posed, scanned images (labeled), 1998 (Box 1.8, Folder 24)
        - Homecoming: Candids and posed (unlabeled), 1999 (Box 1.8, Folder 25)
          32 4x6 color w/negatives and one postcard
        - Homecoming: Candids and posed (unlabeled), 2000 (Box 1.8, Folder 26)
          19 4x6 color, contact sheet w/negatives
        - Athletics: Women's basketball, Dec 1996 (Box 2, Folder 72)
          18 4x6 color w/negatives
        - Alternate Spring Break, Mexico, outdoor group (unlabeled), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 73)
        - Variety Show: Prof. John Murphy, Mr. Carl Pettersch, Dr. Cook, Mr. Chester Floyd, Felix Bonacci, Chet Chiska?, Ken Wright, Wendell Clark, Jean Albright, Joseph Mauro, Tom Costello, Edward McGivern, Bill McKee, Louis Lubus, Joseph Allo, Red McColgan, Bob Anthony, Herb Garber, Warren Jagush, Tom McDonough, Ronald Passerella, Don Morrow, Vincent Stranieri, Will McCarthy, Vin DeFlumeri, Norm Kaback, Ron Passarelli, Paul Petrick, Charlie Mortara, Harry White, Paul Fako, John Murphy, Felix Bonacci, Edwin Kramer, Herbert Garber, Bill Nyerick., 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 74)
          48 4x5 b/w (Donated by Muriel Sesselmann Winzer)
      - Negatives and Miscellaneous
        - Negatives: Echo Reunion, ca.2000 (Box 1.8, Folder 28)
          35 mm color negatives
        - Negatives: Unknown (unlabeled), ca.2000 (Box 1.8, Folder 29)
        - Staff: Cindy Strum, posed, 1997 (Box 1.8, Folder 30)
        - Successfully Applying Your Art After Graduation from WestConn, Apr. 9, 2002 (Box 1.8, Folder 31)
- Series II: Development
  - Capital Campaign, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Hunt Hill Farm Trust, Inc., 2002-2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Pamphlets, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - WestConntributors, 2005-2009 (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
  - Western Connecticut State University Foundation, Inc., 1977-2009 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - University Foundation of Western Connecticut, Inc. Financial Statements and Schedules, 1994, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - University Foundation of Western Connecticut Clippings, 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10a)
  - University Foundation of Western Connecticut Board of Directors Meeting December 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 10b)
  - Scholarship and Awards Recepients, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    35 5x7 color, posed labeled/unlabeled. Images include recipients of:
    Ancell Dean's Award; ATMI Award; Distinguished Alumna Award; SAS Dean's Award; SVPA Dean's Award; SPS Dean's Award; Trybulec Award; President's Award; Citation for Heroism; WCSU Foundation Scholarship; Kenneth Fryer Scholarship; Macricostas Family Scholarship (two awards); Steve Neuwirth Honors Program; Steve Neuwirth American Studies Scholarship; Hancock Scholarship (three awards); Grolier/Dane Cirilli Direct Marketing Scholarship; Gino Arconti Constitutional Law Scholarship; Isabelle T. Farrington Scholarship (two awards); WCSU Emeriti; Colleen Stewart Memorial Scholarship; Bruce Goldsen Scholarship; Union Savings Bank, Thomas R. Nolan Scholarship; Veronica Hogmen Memorial Scholarship; William Walton Scholarship; Ruth Haas Stutz; Ruth Haas Scholarsip; Roger Winward Scholarship; Robert Schappert Scholarship; John Tamas Memorial Scholarship; Esadora George Scholarship; Two unlabeled.
  - Alumni Golf Classic, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    22 5x7 color, candids/posed, labeled/unlabeled (Herpaz, Czajkowski, Ryan, Molinaro, McInerney, Stumpf, McNiff, Roach, Steve Tranzillo, Rodrigue, Mullane, Volpe, Rizzo, Shepperd, O'Brien, Marcinek, Tom Crucitti, Niel Wagner, Montalto, Gage, Ron Pugliese, President Schmotter)
- Series III. University Relations
  WestConn MediaMentions removed in 2011 and transferred to the Western Connecticut State University clippings collection.
  - 2. Office of Public Relations
    - Announcement of merger between Office of Public Relations and University Publications & Design., 2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Calendar of Events (monthly), 2000- (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Experts Guide, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Speakers Bureau (1972), undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Promotional Calendar, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Retirement Booklet, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Groundbreaking of the Westside classroom building (June 3, 1979) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Groundbreaking of Ella Grasso Hall (October 30, 1981)(w/ photographic negatives) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - President Stephen Feldman, 1977-1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Feldman Farewell Luncheon, June 4, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Edwin Goldberg Honor Lunch, November 1985 (w/ photographs) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters and flyers, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Western Connecticut State University & the Community, 1997; RG7_3_16_x (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Western Matters, fall, 1999; RG7_3_17_x (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Item 1)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Item 2)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Item 3)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Item 4)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Item 5)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1954 (Box 5, Item 6)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1954 (Box 5, Item 7)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1954 (Box 5, Item 8)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1955 (Box 5, Item 9)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1955 (Box 5, Item 10)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1955 (Box 5, Item 11)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1956 (Box 5, Item 12)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1956 (Box 5, Item 13)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1956 (Box 5, Item 14)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Item 15)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Item 16)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Item 17)
    - First Weekly Bulletin, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 11, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 12, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 13, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 14, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 15, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 16, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 17, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 18, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 19, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 13-14)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 20, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 21, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 22, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 23, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 6-8)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 24, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 9-11)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 25, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 12-15)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 26, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 16-19)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 27, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 28, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 29, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 22-24)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 30, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 31, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 32, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 33, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 34, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 36, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 37, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 38, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 39, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 40, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 41, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 42, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 43, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 44, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Staff Bulletin vol. 45, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Academic Planner, 1994-1998; RG7_7_1_x (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Public Relations Director Misc., 1996-1997; RG7_7_2_x (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, Nov 1995-May 1996; RG7_7_3_x (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases 1 of 2, Apr 1994-Jun 1994; RG7_7_4_x (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases 2 of 2, Apr 1994-Jun 1994; RG7_7_5_x (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Press Releases 1 of 2, Jul 1994-Sep 1994; RG7_7_6_x (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases 2 of 2, Jul 1994-Sep 1994; RG7_7_7_x (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases 1 of 2, Jan 1994-Mar 1994; RG7_8_1_x (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases 2 of 2, Jan 1994-Mar 1994; RG7_8_2_x (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, Oct 1993-Dec 1993; RG7_8_3_x (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases, Jul 1993-Sep 1993; RG7_8_4_x (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, Apr 1993-Jun 1993; RG7_8_5_x (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Press Releases 1 of 2, Jan 1993-Mar 1993; RG7_9_1_x (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases 2 of 2, Jan 1993-Mar 1993; RG7_9_2_x (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 1989-1992 Highlights, RG7_9_3_x (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Strategic Planning Workshop, 1990; RG7_9_4_x (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Cook, Dr. F. Burton, Fund, 1980; RG7_14_1_x (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Honors Assembly, 1967-1978; RG7_14_2_x (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Isham, Dr. Charlotte, History of WestConn manuscript, ca.1970; RG7_14_3-4_x (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
    - Mailing Lists (Dr. Bersi), 1975-1981; RG7_14_5-7_x (Box 4, Folder 20-22)
    - Summer Theater, 1983; RG7_14_8_x (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Press Releases (January-April 2000), RG7_9_5_x (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Printed Materials, 2000-2004; RG7_9_6_x (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Printed materials, 2005-2007; RG7_9_7_x (Box 9, Folder 7)